[{"answer": "He'll agree with you. Tell me, what do you between the time my friend goes in and comes out? Just huddle in that doorway and wait", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " You see the play? You've seen the play every performance?  But, don't you find it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "The minute it gets printed they're gonna fire on that place all over again..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I never played that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Just wondered what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Just wondered what", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Something maybe grew a size bigger", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I couldn't get into the girdle in two an' a half hours..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hello.", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Call, what call", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " my friend? Have I gone crazy, my friend", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "That I am..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Happy birthday, darling..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Many happy returns of the day..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You don't like Eve, do you", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "An answer", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Like an agent with one client", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Well... let's say she thinks only about you, anyway..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Now who's show up at this hour? It's time people went home", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Discouraging, isn't it? Women with furs like that where it never gets cold..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Don't worry too much about that. my friend just doesn't miss performances. If she can walk, crawl or roll", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, dear. my friend must go on.  As a matter of fact, I see no reason why you shouldn't be my friend's understudy..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, dear. my friend must go on.  As a matter of fact, I see no reason why you shouldn't be my friend's understudy..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I think she would cheer", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I won't forget", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "These s", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What makes a man walk into a lion cage with nothing but a chair", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " To put me to bed? Take my clothes off, hold my head, tuck me in, turn off the lights, tiptoe out...? eve would. Wouldn't you, Eve", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I wouldn't like", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You mustn't mind my friend too much, even if I do..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "The reason is my friend and don't try to figure it out. my friend couldn't", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "And too many of them are produced", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You have me confused with my friend. You go sit by the piano.  And you come sit by me.  Good night", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " That French ventriloquist taught you a lot, didn't he", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "The only thing I ordered by mistake is the guests.  They're domestic, too, and they don't care what they drink as long as it burns... where's my friend? He's late", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "She's a girl of so many interests", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "She's a girl of so many rare qualities", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's a pretty rare quality these days", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "So she seems", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Of course it's funny", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Thirty minutes, forty minutes! What of it", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Stop calling her a kid! It so happens there are particular aspects of my life to which I would like to maintain sole and exclusive rights and privileges", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "For instance", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You've heard of her great interest in the Theate", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Then you two must have a long tal", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " \"Liebestraum", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Play it again", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I don't know if this would be a wise move..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I promise", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Don't you think it's about time it became important", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Don't be evasive", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Spoken like an author.  my friend, I'm not twentyish. I am not thirtyish. Three months ago, I was forty years old. Forty. Four oh.  That slipped out, I hadn't quite made up my mind to admit it. Now I feel as if I'd suddenly taken all my clothes off..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "... as young as they want, you mean. And I'm not interested in whether thousands of people think I'm six or six hundre", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Eve! My understudy..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": " Of course I knew", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Don't mix your metaphors", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Okay. Mix", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Okay. Mix", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "What a body, what a voice", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I'm nothing but a body with a voice. No mind", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "The e", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "The e", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I will not calm down", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "The gong rang. The fight's over. Calm down", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Don't calm down", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "It's obvious you're not a woman", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Well, I am", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "It's not nonsense", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I wish it were", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "But if I tell you it is", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Then what would be enough?  If we were married", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "What about my friend", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "More than anything in this world, I love my friend. And I want my friend. I want him to want me. But me. Not my friend. And if I can't tell they apart", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " - little things here and there, it doesn't matter. You can be proud of yourself, you've got a right to be", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I'll admit I was worried when my friend called. I had my doubts", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": " Are you proud of me, my friend", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "You shouldn't have had any doubts", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": " A fine old theater, the Shubert. Full of tradition, untouched by the earthquake", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "my friend what", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "From the smartness of your dress, I take it your luncheon companion is a lady", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "my friend? Lunching in public", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Where'd you get all that information", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Eve", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "I was wondering whether you'd come at all.", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "I don't expect you to be pleasant", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Don't get up.  And don't act as if I were the queen mother", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "I don't intend to be", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": " In a way. You find yourself trying to say what you mean, but somehow the words change", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "No! I don't expect you to believe anything. Except that the responsibility is mine. And the disgrace", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "I discussed it very openly. I told her that I had spoken to my friend", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "Oddly enough", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "Nothing much. She apologized", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "With tears", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "You know what I'm going to be", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "A married lady", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": " Stop rehearsing your column... Isn't it strange, my friend? I thought I'd be pani", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "Aren't you", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "So that's it. my friend. Still just the Theater, after all..", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "I know nothing about my friend and his loves", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "I know nothing about my friend and his loves", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "my friend is commercially the most successful playwright in that plac", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": "Belong", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": "... taken it for granted? That you and I..", "qsentId": 106}, {"answer": "Probably not", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 109, "question": "What report? To whom", "qsentId": 108}, {"answer": "How do you know my name", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 111, "question": "And what is your name", "qsentId": 110}, {"answer": "And what is your name", "docId": "All-About-Eve.txt", "asentId": 113, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 112}]